<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent" android:paddingLeft="@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin"
    android:paddingRight="@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin"
    android:paddingTop="@dimen/activity_vertical_margin"
    android:paddingBottom="@dimen/activity_vertical_margin"
    tools:context="me.unrealdimension.project1.help">

    <EditText
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:id="@+id/editText"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_alignParentRight="true"
        android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
        android:editable="false"
        android:enabled="true"
        android:text="‘CEG 4410: Golf Buddy’ Subsystem Features include:"
        android:textAlignment="center" />

    <EditText
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:id="@+id/editText2"
        android:layout_alignParentRight="true"
        android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:editable="false"
        android:enabled="true"
        android:text="* Calorie Counter: user has the ability enable this calorie counter from a feature selection menu. Feature is designed to calculate calorie burn over a designated time interval.\n\n* Distance Feature: user has the ability enable a distance tracker from a feature selection menu. Feature is designed to calculate and store the distance traveled in miles over a designated time interval.\n\n* Step Counter: user has the ability enable this step counter from a feature selection menu. Feature is designed to track the amount of steps taken over a designated time period.\n\n* Timer: user has the ability enable the timer from a feature selection menu. Feature is designed to track duration of each specific fitness session.\n\n* Average Speed: user has the ability to select the average speed calculator from a feature selection menu. Feature is designed to calculate the average speed a user has moved after the fitness session in complete. Calculations determined are in miles per hour.\n\n**Feature Selection Menu lists every available feature and can be access by tapping the appropriate buttons for use of each service."
        android:layout_below="@+id/editText" />

</RelativeLayout>
